<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui='urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder'
             xmlns:g='urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui'
             xmlns:c="urn:import:org.aksw.TripleCheckMate.client.widgets">
    <ui:style>
        .smaller-txt {
            text-size: smaller;
            color: #ccc;
        }
    </ui:style>
    <g:HorizontalPanel spacing="5">
        <g:VerticalPanel spacing="4">
            <g:HTMLPanel>
                <h2>What is it about?</h2>
                <p>Welcome to the DBpedia Evaluation Campaign. This campaign aims at
                    evaluating DBpedia resources in order to assess and thereby improve
                    the quality of DBpedia.
                </p>
                <h2>How does it work?</h2>
                <p>First, please authenticate yourself with a google account. This
                    will not only help prevent spam but also help us keep track of how
                    many resources you evaluated. After you click “Start”, you will be
                    provided with a list of classes from DBpedia wherein you may choose
                    the ones you are most familiar with. There are three options: (1)
                    Any: where a completely random resource will be retrieved, (2)
                    Class: where you have the option to choose any class from the
                    DBpedia ontology and a random resource belonging to that class will
                    be retrieved, (3) Manual: where you can manually put in the DBpedia
                    URI of a resource of your choice.
                </p>
                <p>After selecting a resource, you will be shown each triple
                    belonging to that resource on a single row. You need to look at
                    each
                    triple and evaluate whether it contains an error or not. If it
                    contains an error, check the box “has error”. Then, you need to
                    choose an error type from a list. If the error type does not match
                    any of the existing types, you have the option to provide a new
                    type
                    in the “Comments” field. Optionally, you may also write the
                    correct
                    form of the triple in the “Comments” field.
                </p>
                <p>You need to evaluate a minimum of 3 resources. Evaluating one
                    resource may take about 10 - 15 minutes, on average. You need to
                    finish evaluating one resource in one session. You can come back
                    later and evaluate another one. After evaluating one entire
                    resource, click on “Submit”. You should receive a confirmation
                    message.
                </p>
                <h2>How is it going to help?</h2>
                <p>The more the resources you evaluate, the more errors will be
                    detected. These errors will then be recorded and analyzed by our
                    team. Based on whether the error is fixable or not, we will amend
                    DBpedia to ensure that the next versions do not have the same types
                    of errors.
                </p>
                <h2>What do you get?</h2>
                <p>In order to thank you for your contributions, a lucky winner will
                    win either a Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 or an Amazon voucher worth 300
                    EU!
                    So, go ahead, start evaluating now!
                </p>
            </g:HTMLPanel>
            <g:HorizontalPanel spacing="4" addStyleNames="float-right">
                <g:Button ui:field="btnAuth">Authenticate with Google (*)</g:Button>
                <g:Button ui:field="btnStart">Start</g:Button>
            </g:HorizontalPanel>
            <g:HTML addStyleNames="float-right {style.smaller-txt} ">(*) Authentication is required to
                prevent
                spam and give attribution to evaluators
            </g:HTML>
            <g:HTML>
                <h2>Help</h2>
                <p>
                    Here is a short screen cast explaining how you can use this tool
                </p>
                <p>
                    <iframe width="560" height="315"
                            src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/l-StthTvjFI" frameborder="0"
                            allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
                </p>
                <p>
                    You can also visit our dedicated Google Group:
                    <a href="https://groups.google.com/d/forum/dbpedia-data-quality">
                        https://groups.google.com/d/forum/dbpedia-data-quality
                    </a>
                    .
                </p>
            </g:HTML>


        </g:VerticalPanel>
        <g:VerticalPanel width="430px">
            <g:HorizontalPanel width="100%" spacing="4">
                <g:HTML>
                    <h2>Hall of Fame</h2>
                </g:HTML>
                <g:Button ui:field="btnRefreshStats" addStyleNames="float-right">Refresh</g:Button>
            </g:HorizontalPanel>
            <g:ScrollPanel height="800px">
                <c:UserStatisticsTable ui:field="wdgUserStatTable"></c:UserStatisticsTable>
            </g:ScrollPanel>
            <g:HTML addStyleNames="float-right {style.smaller-txt} ">(*) The score table is subject to change
                in the case of false submissions
            </g:HTML>
        </g:VerticalPanel>
    </g:HorizontalPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
